[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
[Jooyoung sighs]
(Jooyoung) Oh my, oh my
[TV sound]
Oh my
[Jooyoung sighs]
[Jooyoung’s light sigh]
Come on, oh my
[TV sound]
Won't you wake up?
I'm folding laundry, laundry, can't you see?
Wow, this is real, sir.
(Lee Young) Why are you going to wear these shoes?
[Jooyoung sighs]
(Jooyoung) Aren’t you going to wash the dishes?
(Lee Young) Later
We're going to have dinner. We can do it together.
(Jooyoung) How about cleaning the bathroom?
I'll do it in the shower
Living expenses?
[Coin falling sound effect]
(Jooyoung) You didn’t come in yesterday?
When are you going to send it?
(Lee Young) Oh, pay off your debt.
I don't give it to you because I don't have it.
Give it until tomorrow, before I kick you out
sister
I'm dying from exhaustion too
Is it easy to force yourself to go to the hospital?
Time doesn't pass anymore
Are you like this outside too?
(Jooyoung) I don’t want to do it, so I look like I’m going to die
Do you only choose hateful words?
Even in the hospital, huh?
Not like that in the hospital
Right?
Are you doing well in society?
no
(Lee Young) I’m not good at it
I can't do that well
That's what I'm saying
Buy me just one outfit
Have a good social life
(Jooyoung) It sounds like clothes.
Hey, your brother-in-law
Wear it until the collar rips
What kind of clothes does the debtor wear?
[Door lock button sound]
[Sound of door opening]
- (Jooyoung) Master is here.
- (Lee Young) My brother-in-law is here.
[Sound of door closing]
You should also do some exercise
Don't lie around like a zombie every Sunday
If you run after those brothers, you're in the emergency room.
Brother-in-law, the package arrived.
I left it on the dressing table in the master bedroom.
(Seungwon) Oh, thank you
Should we eat out today?
(Jooyoung) Eating out?
(Seungwon) Is that so? It’s been a while since we’re all together?
I drink cold ginseng to commemorate receiving my salary.
My brother-in-law likes cold ginseng.
I'm dead
Dowon likes cold ginseng.
Oh, did you?
Do you have similar tastes as me?
(Do-won) Sister-in-law
I think we're out of bottled water?
I didn't even have beer, so I'll get it when I come in.
(Joo Won) Where are you going? What about dinner?
What about cold ginseng?
I need to go to the hospital
Oh, why?
Why, why? I wonder if the master has some business.
(Lee Young) It’s Sunday
Oh, why do you have work on Sunday?
yo. this?
[Dowon’s refreshing elasticity]
(Dowon) I’m sorry, that’s how it happened.
What about cold ginseng?
[Dowon’s sigh]
Can’t it be eaten by three people?
- (Seungwon) Is that so?
- (Jooyoung) Then
[Sound of door opening]
They say Oh Yi-young is shooting.
Now that I'm talking, I have to eat it.
[Jooyoung’s happy laughter]
(Lee Young) I have a promise
(Jooyoung) Huh?
I also have dinner plans
Want to eat cold ginseng?
When did I?
Oh, this bastard is real, Mr.!
[humorous music]
[Seungwon’s light sigh]
[Jooyoung sighs]
It's Sunday and I'm meeting you at the hospital.
Do you have any appointments?
yes, there is
That's how it happened
(Dowon) Are you playing music?
yes
(Dowon) Open up
You said you would play it?
(Do-won) Ah, I don’t listen to music much.
I'm telling you, if you're bored with your in-laws, you should do it.
Um, you don't like music.
I like bread
White bread, red bean bread, cream bread, soboro
I like them all
[lively music]
(Lee Young) I like tteokbokki and kimbap.
I don’t really like sundae.
I really like getting massages
I really hate running, walking, and hiking.
I'm good at swimming though
I'm from the Dolphin Swim Team.
That's why I like the sea better than the mountains.
Am I too loud?
Does it interfere with driving?
Oh, it's okay, I wasn't listening.
(Dowon) It’s Sunday so there’s less traffic.
Yesterday, when I went to work, it was very crowded.
I almost was late
[Lee Young clears his throat]
But why go to the hospital on Sunday?
With teacher Myung-won Myeong-won
We decided to do a thesis together.
(Dowon) I’m going to do a chart review.
I just don't have time on weekdays
I don't have time to search unless it's the weekend.
No, why are you doing it together?
I have to say I won't do it.
How can you say you don't do it?
Come to your senses, bachelor in law.
If you let your guard down for a moment
At some point, you'll be doing it alone, right?
Oh, no way
Ah, it's frustrating
(Do-won) Well, you may have a hard time, but
Wouldn’t it still be helpful to me?
And they say I will be listed as the first author.
There's nothing bad about it
They say he's a yes man and the former class president.
Sounds good, right?
Those are all the same words as hogu.
That's why my nickname is 'Hogu'
Hogu Dowon, isn’t it funny?
If you look at that in-law bachelor,
- He’s handsome, right?
- (Lee Young) Yes
[lively music]
Oh no?
Oh, I guess I'm crazy, what are you saying?
(Do-won) If you look at your in-laws,
- (Lee Young) Are you pretty?
- (Dowon) Ugh, it’s really funny.
Of all the women I've ever seen
It's the funniest
It's never been funny, so what's funny?
Ah, why is it so funny!
(Dowon) Look, it’s funny.
Uh, speaking as well.
Uh, the reaction
[Motorcycle engine sound]
[tire rubbing sound]
[Dowon’s surprised sigh]
[Exciting music]
(Dowon) Are you okay?
It's not okay
[Lee Young sighs]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
[Coffee grinder operating sound]
(Jae-il) Thank you
uh?
hello?
[Jaeil’s refreshing elasticity]
(Dahye) Did you sleep well?
We couldn't sleep because we were on duty.
[Dahye's light smile]
(Jae-il) Ah, yes
But Jaeil, why did you come so early?
(Jaeil) Oh, that’s right
First-year students have a lot to do in the morning.
(Dahye) My hands are still a little slow
It takes a long time
(Eunmi) Ah
yes, that's right
[Dahye's light smile]
(Eunmi) You’ve had a hard time
They say the first year is the hardest.
[Dahye sighs]
But
It's harder in the second year
And in the third year, it gets even harder
Yes, today will be difficult, because every day is difficult.
[Eunmi’s hearty laughter]
[Eunmi and Dahye sigh]
Shall we go then?
- (Dahye) Yes
- (Japan) Ah
Teacher Goo Do-won came.
Shall we buy some coffee?
(Eunmi) Huh? Mmm
I already drank it, 30 minutes ago
(Dahye) Now
Photosynthesis time on the bench in front of these stairs
No, how do you know that?
OBGYs all know this, right?
Teacher Gu Do-won
Where and what are you doing every hour, every day?
[Eye blinking sound effect]
[Interesting music]
(Eunmi) Every morning at 5 o’clock
I eat breakfast and work first.
(Dowon) Hello?
(Dahye) At the basement convenience store during the surgery period
I had a sweet red bean bun and a shot of canned coffee and went to work again.
[Sound effect of clock hands moving]
(Eunmi) Rice is always served clockwise.
Lunch the day after snack
Food the next day, food the next day.
[Sparkling sound effect]
Snack!
(Eunmi) That’s right
Gym in front of the hospital on Mondays
Playing tennis in front of the hospital on Wednesday
And back to the hospital
Wow
You are a completely new routine guy.
Write, you’re not a freshman, are you?
Living in a hospital...
Illness... Illness?
Byeongsaeng?
[Dahye and Eunmi’s laughter]
- (Dahye) Shall we go?
- (Eunmi) Let’s go
- (Jaeil) Oh, I'll take it.
- (Eunmi) Yes
(Jaeil) Give it to me
Give it to me, give it to me
[light music]
[Sound of automatic door opening]
[Sound of automatic door closing]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
(Nanjing) Hi, good morning
- (Sabi) What are your clothes?
- (Namkyung) Huh?
Hey, what the heck
Can you take the elevator?
[Lee Young sighs]
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Sound of elevator opening]
[Sound of running footsteps]
(Seokmin) Oh, wait a minute.
(Nanjing) Wait a minute
Oh, are you going to the 5th floor?
yes
(Nanjing) Thank you
(Seokmin) Yes
[Exciting music]
[shy laughter]
(Lee Young) Why are you hitting me?
[Elevator arrival sound]
Oh, I really don't like male relationships.
(Lee Young) What do you mean?
I think that teacher likes me
Is it true? really?
(Lee Young) I don’t think so at all.
Is that right?
I see, I go first.
Oh, really
(Nankyung) Really 100%
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Soft music]
(Sunbin) Oh, stop looking back.
What if someone misunderstands?
I thought you liked me
Did I do that?
(Sunbin) Yesterday at the cafe
I'm with people at our hospital.
I keep glancing
Chi, do you like me that much?
(Seokmin) Yes
[Sunbin’s light smile]
Wow, am I this obvious type of person?
I didn't know
[Sunbin’s light smile]
(Seonbin) Oh, Professor Yong Seok-min
It's the same short gown.
Something strangely different?
What, it's the same
Ah, the professor only talks, he’s the youngest.
Jjabari
[Seokmin clicks his tongue]
No, but write another thesis, okay?
(Seokmin) How many are there already?
There's a lot to study
[light laughter]
I just need to get the materials and go quickly.
Professor Chae Song-hwa, please wait.
Even so, Professor Chae Song-hwa
You called early in the morning
(Seokmin) Even if you make excuses and rush
Be sure to feed me before sending me off.
Really?
(Seokmin) Oh, anyway, it’s really a ghost.
What is it, professor, my heart is pounding?
You should give me a heart attack
Wow!
(Seokmin) Why, do you feel it?
no
I'm really excited
[Seokmin’s exclamation]
[Sunbin and Seokmin’s laughter]
[Elevator arrival sound]
(Namkyung) Oh, I didn’t even say anything.
Do you know how to get to the 5th floor?
Since when?
(Lee Young) When the resident goes to work
5th floor medical branch, where are you going?
It's not just today?
Yesterday at lunch
I met you by chance at a cafe.
(Sabi) After lunch, go to a cafe...
(Namkyung) Ah, I felt like I was possessed while drinking.
He grinned at me
Go again and turn around
I saw it again and laughed
(Lee Young) Let’s see what’s funny about you
Same today too
No, how can we meet there?
(Namkyung) Ah, I guess I was just timing it.
(Lee Young) Go ask, do you like it?
(Namkyung) Oh, what are you asking? You know it when you see it
(Sabi) How?
(Namkyung) I keep looking at you and smiling
Your body reacts before your head.
What could it be?
It's love
When you like someone, you don't say it with words.
Without realizing it
It just comes out in action.
Like an uncontrollable sneeze
[Jaeil's sneezing sound]
(Japan) Huh, is it a cold?
[Jaeil clears his throat]
The National Assembly meeting is at 6:30, right?
I'm dying because I have so much to do.
What kind of meeting are you having this morning?
I have to do it
I have more than just one or two suggestions to make.
(Lee Young) Look at this surgical gown.
I washed it so hard that the bottom of my pants were torn.
and on-call allowance
Isn’t that the extent of labor exploitation?
It makes no sense to freeze for several years
A meeting of the National Assembly is not a meeting like that.
So, what are you doing?
What are you discussing?
(Namkyung) You really don’t know?
Are you asking because you don’t know?
(Lee Young) What is the theme of the meeting?
you
[Interesting music]
[Dahye sighs]
These are some of the many reports.
It's the tip of the iceberg
(Dahye) The first
April 22nd Professor Junmo Cho
Shouting with GS Arrangement Delay
Who are you on this day?
It's not like a shower
He seemed a bit irritated.
[Dahye sighs]
sorry
second
(Dahye) April 24th Professor Joonmo Cho
Delay in echocardiography of patients
I'm angry all the way to the top
The major gets scolded loudly. Is this even possible?
I said I was sorry right away.
- (Nanjing) Apples are also quick.
- (Jae-il) Be quiet
(Dahye) This is why
Can we not have a National Assembly meeting?
Ah, Professor Joon-mo Jo.
Even when it comes to being impatient, our hospital is number one.
He hates delay the most in the world.
Can’t you do that one thing correctly?
all right!
It's not just teacher Oh I-young who is the problem.
(Dahye) 1st year students
Overall, a few things to point out:
Not even saying hello to seniors
Even if it's a little difficult, I'll pay it forward
No, if possible
Smiling at something I'm told to do
Could you please give me an answer?
(together) yes
(Jae-il) Wow, he’s the scariest among the old guys.
(Nanjing) Youngkorn, Youngkorn
Teacher Oh I-young?
You can do it, right?
yes
(Lee Young) But
It's hard, but how can you show that it's hard?
Is it possible not to pay?
[Program operation sound effect]
(Dahye) What?
(Lee Young) No, we too
I'm not doing it because I want to show off, but like this
Because it shows automatically
[Sound of door opening]
(Dowon) Wasn’t the study time at 7 o’clock?
Why did you come so early?
(Eunmi) What about rice?
Did we eat first year?
(Dahye) Hello, teacher
(Dowon) Yeah, what were you all doing?
[Sound of door closing]
Dahyeya
(Dahye) Yes?
Surely the National Assembly has been revived again?
[Baby laughing sound effect]
[Dahye's awkward laughter]
[humorous music]
Such senseless public executions are prohibited.
I got rid of it the hard way
So don't hold a meeting like that.
(Do-won) Don’t attend.
Okay?
(Dahye) Yes, I understand.
Yes, I should, right?
(together) yes
(Dowon) Oh, that’s right
The mother
I heard you left this at the ward.
Because he’s a male resident teacher, but I’m not.
Oh, Eomjju!
Me? Are you giving it to me?
(Dowon) He said he was so grateful.
I want to post on ‘Praise’
I heard you wrote down your name too?
Professor Seo Jeong-min
You're shooting me because I'm in a bad mood after a long time.
- I’ll eat well, Eom Jae-il.
- (Residing in Japan) Yes
Chorong’s mother lives in Mapo.
She runs a flower shop and her husband is a car dealer.
(Dowon) Oh, right, he
But if Eom Jae-il becomes the main character in ‘Praise’
Isn’t this the first year of obstetrics and gynecology?
- (Eunmi) That’s right.
- (Dowon) Huh?
[lively music]
I haven't been able to do it either.
First time? Really?
Probably so?
[Jaeil’s happy exclamation]
- (Nanjing) Congratulations
- (Lee Young) Congratulations
(Sabi) It’s not done yet.
I'll celebrate when I'm done
whatever it is
[Jaeil’s light smile]
Of course I am private
(Sabi) When you say ‘I praise you’
I don't know how to evaluate medical knowledge or research achievements.
Isn’t this a good thing for evaluating life in a medical country?
The first half of the year will be evaluated soon.
(Namkyung) Hey, I guess the professors won’t be that interested?
My friend's hospital
They say they give a coffee coupon worth 20,000 won per transaction.
[Clapping hands]
(Jaeil) Is that important?
the patient
The point is that you were comforted by my words.
[Lee Young yawns]
Too much for the patient
They tell me not to empathize, but
I think you need to do some
(Namkyung) What did you do?
(Jay) Um...
When dealing with these mothers
Sincerely
Empathizing with the mother's feelings
Even if I say a word warmly
This shows that words are really important...
Oh, I see.
(Lee Young) I go first
(Residence in Japan) No...
[cell phone closing sound]
(Namkyung) I thought it was something great again
See you later
(Jaeil) Isn’t this great?
Even if you give me a tip
To speak warmly?
If I do that too
Can you become the main character of ‘Praise’?
Then
[Sparkling sound effect]
patient
maternal body
[Program operation sound effect]
(Jay) Ah...
It's the first time I've been asked to go to a big hospital.
[Junmo’s sigh]
You've probably already heard it, but...
Biopsy results
You have been diagnosed with endometrial cancer.
(Junmo) The cancer mass in this uterus is
It's a little big
Preserving the uterus is a bit difficult.
[Sunmi mocks crying]
I heard it seems to have spread to the ovaries. Is that correct?
(Junmo) Uh, on both ovaries
There is something that looks like a lump
But as of now, this is
Is it cancer that has spread from the endometrium?
Or is it just plain nonsense?
I don't know
Write, these ovaries before surgery
Because biopsy is not possible
A biopsy should be performed during surgery.
Then you will know exactly
[Sunmi mocks crying]
(Sunmi) No...
Cancer?
[Embarrassed laughter]
I'm sorry, teacher.
my mom is still
I'm not mentally ready
[Sunmi mocks crying]
It's okay
(Jun’s mother) First of all, please be hospitalized.
Have an MRI and CT scan
Schedule a surgery date as soon as possible
I think it would be a good idea to look at the ovaries accurately as well.
[Knocking sound]
Patient Geum Seon-mi
Yes, me.
(Hyejin) I will help you with the MRI test.
Yes, I will go.
[Sunmi mocks crying]
mom
They say you just need to get tested and have surgery.
[Calm music]
(Sunmi) Yes
I even fasted.
I was worried about what would happen if I couldn’t get tested.
Still, get an MRI right away, huh?
That's a relief
[Sunmi mocks crying]
(Sunmi) Mom, I’m okay, right?
I'm fine, but what's wrong with mom?
[Sunmi mocks crying]
What are the symptoms of patient Geum Seon-mi?
Check it carefully
(Dowon) When did irregular bleeding start?
in detail how often it happened
(Lee Young) Yes
It's starting again
Ah!
It's my hobby, hobby
(Dowon) As you know
The surgery was suddenly delayed
You must have been very nervous.
I will go and comfort you well.
I'm not good at that kind of thing, am I?
As the attending physician, to the patient
I'll explain it well and visit often.
Paying a lot of attention, that's comfort
yes, i understand
But
The patient is very brave.
The patient's mother
Even after leaving the treatment room earlier,
You cried for over 30 minutes
I explained it to you.
(Lee Young) You barely heard me.
In that case
As the attending physician, to the guardian
I'll explain it well and visit often.
- (Dowon) Nervous...
- Paying a lot of attention is comforting.
- I know.
- So
(Lee Young) What should I do?
That's because I really don't know
How can you tell me that, I don't know
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Dowon) Yes, let’s go
[Call end tone]
Have a hard time
[Lee Young sighs]
(Patient 1) I saw it on the Internet.
I heard there is a new targeted treatment drug.
Does this apply to me too?
(Namkyung) Ah...
A new anti-cancer drug?
(Patient 1) Yes
Is it because the anti-cancer drugs are too strong now?
My body is very tired and I have no energy.
I think it's because of the medicine.
Is that right?
Oh, I'm still in my first year.
I'll ask and tell you right away.
(Patient 1) Child, true self
How does our teacher
You don’t know more than the patient.
Ah, indeed
[Nanjing’s embarrassed laughter]
(Jae-il) Oh my, mother
(Patient 1) Oh my
(Japan) Are you having a hard time?
Wow
(Jae-Jae) Physical strength is important when undergoing chemotherapy.
You need to eat well and exercise a lot.
Still, it’s better than when you came 3 weeks ago.
You have a nice face, yeah
[Patient 1 laughs]
I didn't see it and thought I would just leave.
[Patient 1’s light smile]
(Patient 1) Oh, that teacher
Especially
This time, my body is tired and I have no energy.
I'm really dying
Mom, you left a lot of food yesterday too, right?
My mouth is bitter, so what should I do?
I'm sick of hospital food now.
Still
You need to eat a lot and exercise a lot.
That's the best, okay?
Okay, I'll do it, I'll do it
[light music]
(Jae-il) I will come tomorrow and check.
- (Patient 1) Child...
- Have you finished eating or not?
(Patient 1) I understand, indeed.
[Jae-il and Patient 1’s light laughter]
Then let's fight
thank you
(Patient 1) Oh, right.
[Patient 1 laughs]
(Japan) Hey
If you look like you don't know anything
Patients will really like it
(Namkyung) Oh, I don’t know, so what should I do?
(Japanese) Child
Everyone in the hospital knows anyway.
We're fools
Even the good transport driver Hwang Min-cheol.
We don't believe it
Anyone who is a first-year resident at this hospital is
there is no one
So this is what I said earlier
It's an in-depth episode with a few warm words.
Baby, tell me this, don't you
Let me know, I'll listen.
Eat well and exercise a lot
What?
(Jaeil) If you’re not sure, just say this
Eat well and exercise a lot
Oh, is that wrong?
That’s right, eat well and exercise a lot.
That's the shortcut to health
Ah, I listened seriously for no reason.
You said something that didn't matter
(Patient 2) Huh? teacher
(Jaeil) No, hello?
How is the pain?
It's still a bit uncomfortable
It's not getting better quickly?
Ah, eat well now.
You need to exercise a lot
Did you exercise a lot today?
I didn't do much
(Jaeil) Oh, that doesn’t work.
You have to do it consistently
Take a walk with me
[Patient 2 laughs]
That's fine then
I also went on a date with my teacher.
[Jae-il and Patient 2’s laughter]
Just go to the annex over there.
[humorous music]
(Patient 2) Yes
(Jae-il) Even when I’m not there
You need to exercise a lot
[Patient 2 laughs]
(Patient 2) Oh, yes, I understand.
(Jae-il) I will check it every day.
[Patient 2 laughs]
(Sunmi) Hey, mom
[Sunmi’s mock sobbing sound]
(Sunmi) Huh?
My hands and feet are fine
(Sunmi’s name) It’s because my mom wants to do it.
Because my mom wants to do it
Ah, indeed
bed by the window
I heard you can fly tomorrow, so just be patient
(Sunmi) Is it nice here?
It's easy to go out into the hallway
What is good?
It's a doorway room.
What kind of doorway is this?
It's close to the nurses and teachers.
The bathroom is right in front too.
My daughter is so kind
(Sunmi) So kind
Why do I only think good things...
[Sunmi sighs]
(Sunmi) It’s starting again, again
[Sunmi’s mock sobbing sound]
I'll be swept away
- (Lee Young) Hello
- (Sunmi) Hello
(Lee Young) Hello
There's nothing uncomfortable, right?
yes, none
It's all good
Uh, I think the surgery will be the day after tomorrow afternoon.
Uh, it's the last time of the day.
If the previous surgery is delayed or an emergency occurs,
It may be later
Oh, I'm starving today because I'm having a test.
I will be fasting until late on the day of surgery.
Then he doesn't have stamina.
(Sunmi) Can’t I do it on the morning of the surgery?
There are other surgeries ahead.
(Lee Young) Otherwise
I have to postpone the date. Should I postpone it?
[Sunmi mock sigh]
(Sunmi) No, I’ll just do it.
Please stick to your original schedule.
(Lee Young) Ah, yes
(Sunmi) Mom, it’s okay because I’m young.
Please mom, stop fasting and eat something.
Teacher, please say something.
Mom, you need to eat to be healthy.
Be sure to eat it
I'll take care of it.
(Sunmi) Ah, teacher.
How long does the surgery take?
Oh, just the hysterectomy takes an hour and a half.
If ovarian metastasis is confirmed
It will take up to 3 hours
I also had an MRI done earlier.
Can’t you really see that it has metastasized?
Yeah, I can't really tell from that.
No, it's still a major surgery to open the stomach.
Well, I don't know how many hours
I don't even know how much it costs
It doesn't make sense.
But there are many cases like that with wives.
[Sunmi mock sigh]
(Sunmi) What’s going on?
(Sunmi) Mom, it could be good.
Huh? Right, teacher?
The ovaries might be okay, right?
(Lee Young) Uh...
I don't have anything to say right now.
I'll have to have surgery to find out.
[Sunmi mocks crying]
The teacher made my mom cry again.
[Sunmi’s mock sobbing sound]
(Sunmi) Ms. Yang, stop crying.
- (Sunmi) Okay
- (Sunmi) Huh?
(Okim) Oh my, that’s right
I don't know that
The day after tomorrow, huh?
If you just let me be discharged the day after tomorrow, I'll be fine.
Grandma, I don't know that yet.
(Nanjing) I don’t know now
But first, you have to redo the urine line.
The residual urine volume is over 400.
4, 400?
(Okim) Oh, what is that?
Is it over 4 million won?
No, it's urine left in the bladder.
This urine has to come out.
It's not coming out
(Okim) Ome, how did you see it?
[Surprisingly] Oh my gosh
I didn't go out and flush the water.
no
(Namkyung) Uh...
I'll put the urine strip back on later.
I'll check the residual urine volume again tomorrow.
Only when that decreases can you be discharged.
Oh my, what happened?
I have a wedding in 3 days.
(Okim) Ome, what should I do, huh?
Oh my, I’m going to cheat on you before Jungheon’s day.
My family doesn't know I had surgery.
Oh my, how should I use it?
Well, no blackmail, huh?
I had to go to the wedding that day.
Young Master, is there no better way?
I really want to send it to you too
However, if there is a lot of residual urine, you cannot be discharged.
Oh my, my goodness
Why doesn't urine come out when you sweat?
[Nankyung’s embarrassed groan]
(Ok Im) Then, give me some dick medicine, eh?
Whatever it is, please give me some treatment.
I'll be discharged from the hospital in 3 days.
First, you have to watch.
(Okim) What pee!
Omi, are we seeing each other again?
It's not urine, it's residual urine.
grandmother
You don’t eat well, do you?
[humorous music]
(Okim) Dick, that’s...
Oh, I gave it to you as a gift, but you kept it?
(Namkyung) Ah, somehow!
Grandma, eat well and drink a lot of water.
[Clapping hands]
In particular, you need to exercise a lot.
Only then can you be discharged.
(Okim) Oh my gosh, it’s true
I don't know it, huh?
It hurts because my stomach was cut open.
This thing is cold too
The more
You need to eat well and exercise a lot.
[Okim clears his throat]
(Ok Im) Draw it
Handang crab
Go out from today
No, I'll do it right away, don't worry.
yes
(Nankyung) Is it true?
I wasn't Eom Jae-il
I almost stayed up all night with that old lady.
Hey, it's true
It's completely effective
(Japan) Book report and thesis report
What are you doing just filling your head?
Studying is not everything in practice
(Sabi) I want to use it too, but I don’t have the chance.
[Knocking sound]
[Sound of door opening]
(together) hello
(Nanjing) Hello
(Dowon) Oh, you guys have become really close by now?
We leave work together
[Nankyung’s light smile]
- Where are the four of you going?
- (Together) Home.
Yes, ah, there was a house.
Go, then
(Together) Goodbye
You guys...
Aren’t you hungry?
(Sabi) Huh?
(Nanjing) Rice?
Um, shall we have dinner together?
Are you buying it for me?
[Jaeil’s light smile]
[lively music]
I’m thankful that Teacher Oh I-young stayed.
(Dowon) Eat quickly
Thank you so much
Oh, who's left?
If you ask me to eat on the way home from work,
I made a big mistake
Oh, really, I had no idea.
(Dowon) Still, the kids
Don't lie, be honest
I'm glad you asked me to buy it next time
I’m not sorry and the kids aren’t sorry either.
[laughter]
Don’t you know MZ?
Why don’t you know, I’m MZ too
What did you say
But why don’t you get off work?
I need to watch the surgery video
(Lee Young) Yes
Why don't you go?
Ah, let's eat...
I was on my way home from work, right?
(Dowon) That’s right, sorry.
[Dowon’s sigh]
Have you already eaten everything?
(Dowon) Yes, eat slowly.
(Lee Young) No, I’m full.
[light music]
No, if you're going to cut it for 1 minute with soup
Why are we eating together?
No, if you're not going to eat it then
Why did you come, why don’t you go like MZ?
Oh, I'm outside!
I thought they were going to buy me something delicious outside.
(Lee Young) What is the cafeteria, really?
Should I be sorry again?
sorry
Wow, no soul, mr.
[Lee Young’s incredulous breathing]
(Gyeongju Department) Is your name Gyeongju Hwang?
I'm a dad
I received a call that a child had collapsed.
(Nurse 1) Oh, over there.
[Gyeongju groans in pain]
[heavy music]
(Gyeongju Department) Gyeongju
What's going on?
Where does it hurt, huh?
[Gyeongju groans in pain]
(Gyeongju Bu) Does it hurt a lot?
What's going on all of a sudden, huh?
(Gyeongju) Dad, I’m okay.
It's no big deal
[Gyeongju groans in pain]
Dad, go and do some work.
Oh, hurry up
[Gyeongjubu’s sigh]
I was fine until morning.
Where does it suddenly hurt?
Is it your appendix?
Oh, not the appendix.
Then where are you going?
(Sabi) The professor will be here soon.
You just finished your delivery.
Yes?
(Jeongmin) Hello?
Are you in a lot of pain?
Let me take a look at the boat.
[Gyeongjubu’s surprised exclamation]
[Excited breathing]
(Lee Young) To Geum Seon-mi and her guardians
I explained it to you
To another teacher
He said he wanted to hear the explanation again.
(Sunmi) Ah...
Since you say you don't know everything, I
[takes a breath]
I'm so anxious
(Do-won) Then, let’s start with the surgical procedure.
Let me explain again, Mom.
yes
(Dowon) First of all, what I am currently suspecting is
Remove the ovarian nodule first
send out an emergency biopsy
From cancer in the endometrium
It will be removed through a hysterectomy.
Then, according to the results of the ovarian biopsy,
The decision will be made whether to remove the ovaries or not.
(Sunmi) Ah...
Well, then
Among these patients
Because it’s not cancer
There are cases where the ovaries are not removed, right?
As I said
That requires surgery.
you can see
(Sunmi) Oh, no, I mean
If my ovaries are okay
So if you don't remove the ovaries
Um, you can live without hormone treatment, right?
Right?
Yes, when I only had a hysterectomy.
No need for hormone treatment
Oh, then after the surgery
My daughter is just normal
I study again
Is it possible to make a living while working?
Well, after the surgery
I need chemotherapy or radiation treatment.
(Sunmi) Ah...
mother
Are you having a hard time?
Please tell me something is okay
[Sunmi mocks crying]
(Sunmi) It will be okay from now on
What's wrong with not knowing everything?
What did my daughter do so wrong?
[sad music]
[Sunmi mocks crying]
There must be at least one hope
Aren’t you going to at least comfort me that it’s okay?
That way, you'll feel less sorry.
(Dowon) Mother...
[Sunmi mocks crying]
[Knocking sound]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sunmi’s surprised exclamation]
(Sunmi) Who would have cried like this?
Mom!
Everyone came out to watch in the hallway!
Did you send me for a walk here just to do this?
Oh, really
I'm fine
If someone sees it, will they think it's a portrait?
(Sunmi) Says all kinds of things
Is that what you want to say to your mom?
(Sunmi) Okay
Okay, let's go quickly.
I did it to embarrass myself, because of my mom.
[Sunmi’s mock sobbing sound]
I'm sorry, teacher.
[Do-won’s light smile]
(Sunmi) Next time, just
Just explain it to me
Comforting my crying mother
It's because I'm more tired.
Yes, teacher?
Ah...
yes
(Gyeongju Bu) Do you have any thoughts or not?
Hey, Hwang Gyeong-ju
Just say something to your dad, okay?
Oh, because I have an idea.
Aren’t you fooling me this whole time?
[Gyeongjubu’s sigh]
Hey, it's racing
You are now a freshman in college.
Huh? What are you going to do next?
(Sabi) I took anti-uterine contraction medication.
Uh... I watched it for about an hour or two.
(Gyeongju Bu) Aren’t you going to talk to dad?
You're not going to say anything!
Take care of it!
So please go away
If you go?
uh? What if I go?
I don't have a mother, but is there anyone who will come?
(Gyeongju Boo) Is it there?
Oh, that...
I know, huh?
That crazy guy...
[Gyeongjubu’s sigh]
Does that bastard even know?
Wow, I'm crazy, I
Are you really doing this alone?
you
Do you know who you are?
dad!
Father, no, grandfather, calm down a little.
Give me your phone
Give me your cell phone!
It's Gyeongju
[heavy music]
[Gyeongjubu’s sigh]
(Gyeongju Bu) Is that you?
It's you!
you bastard
(Gyeongju) Yeongchan...
(Youngchan) Are you okay?
You waited a long time, right?
[Gyeongjubu’s sigh]
Shall we begin?
[ultrasound sound]
(Jeongmin) Can you hear the heartbeat?
It's growing well at about 2.7kg.
Mom worked hard
Here's the baby's head
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Youngchan) Hello
[Gyeongjubu’s sigh]
(Jeongmin) This is the head
Can you see both the eyes and nose clearly?
(Gyeongju club) Ah...
yes, yes
I see it well
(Jeongmin) The amount of amniotic fluid is also appropriate.
Placenta location is also good.
Baby’s posture is good too
There are currently no unusual findings.
(Japan) Salty
Given by patient Ae-shin Yoon from Haenam.
Every time I see you, I have a daughter and son-in-law
They say they want to make it, haha...
(Lee Young) That daughter came and went yesterday.
(Jay) Huh?
Not just two sons?
Ah
Yeah, I guess you forgot you have a daughter.
(Nanjing) Come and see first.
I told you to pretend to be deceived and just ask.
What is it?
[Bubble sound effect]
[Tense sound effect]
This time
You're the guardian, right?
[Interesting music]
[Nanjing’s surprised exclamation]
(Nanjing) Look
The day comes when you ask me something
(Jae-il) Well, write...
This is quite difficult
The mother and father were very angry.
A person called a boyfriend is a cheap person
Do you feel like running away?
(Lee Young) Yes, Sabi Kim just said that.
[Jaeil makes a noise]
(Japan) This mountain
From baby issues to family issues
It looks very complicated because it overlaps.
Surprisingly, the solution is often easy.
baby crying
[Nankyung’s surprised gasp]
(Jae-il) [Clapping hands] Now, think about your internship.
Even if a mother whom I have never seen gives birth to a baby
I'm crying and my heart is pounding.
It's my child
What if it was your grandson?
Now I hate my daughter
You might be upset because the situation is embarrassing, but
When you hear a baby crying
Will you feel relieved?
Come to think of it
Because the mother and father can hear the heartbeat
I answered for the first time
I think I laughed a little
[Clapping hands] That's it!
(Jae-Jae) My father, no, my grandfather
No, no, the mother and father
Set the sound of a baby crying as BGM
[surprised] Congratulations
If you say the baby is so pretty, it's a happy ending.
- This problem
- (Namkyung) Boyfriend
I came here to ask about my boyfriend.
You suddenly become a father overnight
Isn’t that scary?
You can become a mother overnight too.
[humorous music]
I know, but...
(Jay) My boyfriend didn’t even know I was pregnant.
I didn't have time to prepare at all, and...
Tonight or tomorrow
Wouldn’t it be okay to put your mind together and show up?
(Sabi) If you don’t come
I can't even hear the baby crying.
How easy is it to solve something?
Without even knowing, Mr.
Why are you angry with me?
Ah, you ate it!
(Nankyung) Yes, that’s right!
[Crackling sound effect]
I'll buy it for you tomorrow
[surprised gasp]
Let's go home, it's past work time.
[Jaeil clears his throat]
(Lee Young) I’m going
(Namkyung) At times like this, it’s really fast.
Hey, who is chasing you?
[Knocking on door]
[Sound of door opening]
Oh, where did you go?
(Junmo) Where did Oh Yiyoung go?
I hope they delay the surgery again
You didn't get off work, did you?
[Doridori sound effect]
Ah, I am Mr. Lee.
[Sound of door closing]
[Interesting music]
[Lee Young sighs]
(Junmo) Yes, hello
Oh yes, hello
[Junmo’s sigh]
What are you, huh?
Why does it keep delaying?
In my world, surgery is delayed.
You know what I hate the most, don’t you?
(Lee Young) I know, I’m sorry
(Junmo) I’m sorry about that guy, Mr.
Today, why am I
Do I have to have surgery by this time, huh?
It's a co-op, but even the euros are delayed.
Do you know how much backstory there is?
With heart ultrasound
To test lung function...
What?
I contacted Cardio.
They told me to wait...
I can't even control the inspection schedule.
Just because I have to wait
I'm waiting with excitement now!
Perform a proper examination of the patient
Just in the operating room
Just make sure you get off on time, huh?
Hey, is this difficult?
This isn't basic, it's basic!
Oh, it's just that I can't even do this
You're not saying you don't want to do it, huh?
why? Do you want to do it again?
(Junmo) Do you want to quit again?
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
(Sunmi) Hey, teacher.
I think you should take a look here.
Well, it looks like the injection fluid is leaking.
(Junmo) That...
The nurse will be gone soon
I'll take a look, yeah
I'm in a bit of a hurry, but
Here is our teacher Oh I-young
Can you please take a look?
Is that so?
Sseu-eup, Teacher Oh I-young
Go and take a look
(Junmo) Yes
yes
[Junmo’s sigh]
(Sunmi Mo) Professor
You must be very scared.
You don't do that to us.
(Lee Young) Ah, yes, a little bit
(Sunmi) I was thinking about just going
She's like my daughter
Is there anyone who is good at it from the beginning?
We all learn by making mistakes.
But I did it a lot
(Lee Young) Thank you
(Sunmi) In front of the person who just got scolded
That's not what I want to say
I really like the teacher
Doing what I want to do
I make mistakes and get scolded
[Heavy laughter]
I'm so jealous of it all
[Calm music]
My daughter didn't get sick either.
Where did you get scolded like a teacher?
Then call your mom
I swear at my boss and tell him stories.
[Sunmi mock sigh]
Who can you blame?
Sending the child abroad alone
I didn't even know that my insides were rotting and falling apart.
I got accepted to a good school
I brag about being a lawyer
I don't even have the right to cry
[light laughter]
Just looking at him makes me want to cry
[Sunmi’s wife’s light laughter]
I'm going to stop crying now
That young guy is brave like that too.
The day when the person called mom was fake
I'm crying out loud
What I haven't been able to take care of for you all this time
I'm going to do it all for you
[Calm music - continued]
From now on, stick close to my side
I will never hurt alone again
I have to be a mother now.
(Lee Young) That...
There's nothing I can do for you
Has it metastasized to the ovaries?
Can you let me know as soon as possible?
Professor, when you calm down, I'll ask you a question.
Thank you for your words
(Sunmi) But that’s
I don't think it will be easy
I, by any chance
Can I ask you one more favor?
[light music]
Have you decided?
Plain pong...
No
Please give me warm Americano
(Clerk) A warm Americano.
[Sound effect appears suddenly]
(Japanese) Teacher Gu Do-won said he was shooting, bread.
And a glass of Megalicano.
[Payment sound effect]
- next
- (Namkyung) Oh, I’m okay.
Oh, please add a shot.
[Payment sound effect]
I'm Hot Earl Gray Tea
(clerk) Yes
Crush Plainpong!
Add Honey Pong cereal and add honey.
[Payment sound effect]
(Nanjing) If I don’t quit my job, I’m going to resign.
(Japan) But are you going to the funeral?
Has anyone passed away?
This is blue black, not black?
Tsk, and this is new
I have a blind date today
(Nanjing) I’m 32 years old.
I guess the business hit the jackpot.
What did the car say?
Well anyway
Ah, I really should be doing well today.
Hey, hey, people see it
(Lee Young) I’m not watching, don’t worry.
You take a look in the mirror
How come you become more and more poor?
(Namkyung) Like a child who suddenly went bankrupt
[cell phone ringing sound]
[Lee Young sighs]
(Sabi) Yes
Yes, I'll be right there.
[Lee Young and Jae-il sigh]
[Call end sound]
(Guide voice) Your
My phone is off
[Gyeongjubu’s angry sigh]
[heavy music]
You will be connected to voicemail
[Call end sound]
Your phone is off
[The frustrated elasticity of the Gyeongju club]
[Call end sound]
[angry sigh]
(privately funded) Hwang Gyeong-ju, maternal guardian
Please come to the front of the delivery room.
I think I'm going into labor soon.
Already?
(Minjoo) Mother, are you in a lot of pain?
[Gyeongju groans in pain]
(Jiyoung) New mother, please breathe.
(Gyeongju) Dad, Yeongchan
Yeongchan
(Gyeongju Department) Uh, uh, uh
[Gyeongju groans in pain]
[Call connection tone]
(Guide voice) Your
My phone is off
To voicemail...
[The frustrated elasticity of the Gyeongju club]
[Call end sound]
[Sound of automatic door opening]
[Gyeongjubu’s nervous sigh]
[Newborn baby cries]
(Jiyoung) Gyeongju Hwang, maternal guardian
(Sabi) Father
[Gyeongju’s trembling breathing]
Oh, what about my daughter? What about my daughter?
(Sabi) With the mother
All babies are healthy
[Sigh of relief]
I have 10 fingers and 10 toes.
I'm breathing well and everything is fine.
yes
[Newborn baby cries]
[Calm music]
[Smiling slightly] Thank you
Thank you for your hard work
(private) After the mother is treated,
You'll see it soon
After going to the recovery room, I went straight to the hospital room...
[Sound of running footsteps]
(Youngchan) Wait a minute
[Yeongchan’s heavy breathing]
sorry
Where on earth have you been and are you coming back now?
No, no matter how immature you are
(Gyeongju Bu) Oh, why are you calling again...
[Gyeongjubu’s deep sigh]
(Youngchan) Ah, it’s turned off.
sorry
I tried to bring my mom, but it didn't work out.
(Youngchan) I’m sorry, father.
After hitting him, he relaxed a little.
I will definitely take care of my house.
Convince Mom and Dad
I will definitely bring you to the hospital.
It's true, father.
[Newborn baby cries]
What about racing?
When can we see Gyeongju?
(Sabi) Is the mother okay?
You'll see it soon
[Yeongchan sighs in relief]
(Youngchan) Thank you
[Gyeongjubu’s light sigh]
(Juyeon) Teacher, where do you think you are going?
Yes, how did you know?
I wore my makeup really well today
It’s so bright, isn’t it?
(Juyeon) I feel like a different person
I have a blind date.
Ah, somehow you look so pretty today
(Juyeon) The hair style changed too
It suits you so well
Makeup and outfit coordination are all so pretty
Perfect that japchae
[Embarrassed laughter]
My hair is the same today
(Juyeon) Ah...
(Nanjing) Please tell me
Just one thing before you go
[Awkward laughter]
How is it?
Am I being discharged from the hospital tomorrow?
(Nanjing) I guess until tomorrow morning
I guess we'll have to wait and find out
Ugh, I have to pee again.
(Namkyung) Yes, then
(Ok Im) What time is it in the morning?
Is it very morning, is it late morning?
(Namkyung) Uh...
Wearing a pee line tonight
After taking it out in the morning,
Because 4 hours have to pass
Write, 9 a.m. at the earliest?
Oh, no, between 10 and 11?
Well, it's about 12 o'clock at the latest.
If there are three weddings, I can go.
Oh, you can go for that.
You may not be able to go
[Nankyung’s light smile]
(Okim) Ah, I know that too.
(Nanjing) Grandma, then I
(Okim) Bye bye
A flower has bloomed on our master’s face.
[Okim’s laughter]
Are you going somewhere nice?
Okay, see you tomorrow then.
(Nanjing) Grandma, eat a lot
Exercise a lot too!
(Ok Im) Ying
[Sound of door opening]
- (Nanjing) Just one order from me.
- (Lee Young) I hate it.
(Nanjing) Patient No. 1011, Min Bo-ra
Just one fever reducer
[Keyboard operation sound]
(Lee Young) I hate it
You said you would do it and you did.
Hey, if everything goes well, I'll make a baby.
That's because I don't think it will work out
[Sighing] On your snout
Do you think the devil lives there?
I need to use a talisman
It won't work, right?
(Namkyung) Do it for me just once
Min Bora is a patient, fever reducer.
(Lee Young) I hate it
(Nanjing) Thank you
[Keyboard operation sound]
Min Bora, Min Bora, Min Bora, Min Bora
That's right, room 1011
[Mouse operation sound]
(Residence in Japan) But
‘Praise’ bulletin board
Doesn’t it usually change around the third week?
[cell phone ringing sound]
That's strange
(Lee Young) Yes, professor.
Patient Geum Seon-mi completed all work-ups.
Since the morning, the surgery has been pushed back little by little.
I think the surgery will be done at 7 o'clock.
yes
[Call end sound]
Surgery?
- Who is it, Professor Joon-mo Jo?
- (Lee Young) Oh
If I'm late for surgery today, I'll really die.
[Mouse operation sound]
[lively music]
(Jaeil) Hey, are you going already?
(Lee Young) My guardian asked me something.
(Jae-il) What is it?
What is it?
From the front of the operating room until anesthesia
You asked me to stay with the patient?
(Lee Young) Uh, from there
Because the guardian cannot enter
(Jaeil) That operating room hallway is scary
Than the transfer driver I saw for the first time
The one I saw often is better
(Lee Young) It’s not that difficult.
No way
Just move together
You're not going to say anything, are you?
What are you talking about?
Anything to talk about
I can't do that.
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Elevator button sound]
(Japan) Use it, in those times
(Sunmi’s mother) [Sniffling] Mom, here
Because I will wait
Don't worry about anything, just sleep well.
[Sunmi and Sunmi mock laughter]
[Sorrowful music]
My good and smart daughter
[Sunmi’s whimpering sound]
Everything will be fine, don't worry
I only trust my mom
(Sunmi) Okay
I'm not worried
The teachers will take care of it.
And if you only perform surgery on the uterus, it takes an hour and a half.
Even ovarian surgery can be done in 3 hours.
Soon, soon
1 hour and a half
Finishes in 1 and a half hours
It will happen
Right, teacher?
Ah... yes
I'll have a good surgery
Mom, don't cry outside, okay?
(Sunmi’s name) Mom, don’t cry
Why is mom crying?
Everything will be fine after surgery.
Please take care, teacher.
(Lee Young) Okay, let’s go in now.
[pass tag sound]
(Sunmi) I’ll go and come back
[Sunmi’s light smile]
[Sunmi’s trembling breathing]
(Nurse 2) What is your name?
When did you start fasting?
(Nurse 3) Before going in
Let me check a few things
What is your name?
How much longer can I wait?
(Lee Young) I just need to check personal information.
I'll be in soon
[Newborn baby cries]
(Youngchan) Father, what about me?
my life
I can dedicate it to my child
Oh, you can also dedicate it to Gyeongju
[Sound of automatic door opening]
[Gyeongjubu’s laughter]
(Nurse 4) Hwang Gyeong-ju, baby’s guardian
(Youngchan) Me, I am the father.
[Sound of automatic door opening and closing]
[Newborn baby cries]
[Gyeongjubu’s sigh]
Where have you been, father?
Are you not in the hospital room during the day?
(Gyeongjubu) Oh, yeah, wait a minute.
So...
Congratulations
The baby is really pretty
It looks just like your mother, right?
(Sabi) My boyfriend likes it a lot too.
I think you're already being a fool.
Really congratulations, father.
(Gyeongju Department) I
It should be celebrated, right?
yes?
[Calm music]
In one day
Should I be happy that I became a grandfather?
Oh, for being born healthy
I know I’m thankful too
I know that I am responsible
What a precious life
I know it all too
That baby looks just like my daughter
That innocent baby
(Gyeongju Club) For me,
It's like an angel came to grab my daughter's ankle.
(Lee Young) There are a lot of surgeries, right?
There are so many people getting surgery.
Than Sunmi
Because there are many worse people
(Sunmi) Oh, fellow soldier?
(Lee Young) Yes?
If it's something like that, put it in.
I've heard it too much
(Sunmi) What is comradeship?
I'm the youngest here
I have no luck
(Lee Young) While Sunmi was undergoing surgery
Because I will always be by your side
Take it easy
Why are you acting like a teacher?
Since none of those words can comfort me, I just
Can't you just keep doing what you're doing?
Who ordered that? Right?
(Lee Young) Yes
My classmate is Eom Jae-il.
[Sunmi’s laughter]
[Medical device operation sound]
[Sunmi’s trembling breathing]
(Sunmi) Ah...
Why are you like this?
[Sunmi’s trembling breathing]
Oh, I'm really fine.
[Sunmi’s crying sound]
[Sunmi’s sobbing]
Oh, I'm sorry, teacher.
[Sunmi’s crying]
[sad music]
Oh, sorry.
[Sunmi’s crying]
- (Sanghyun) Patient
- (Lee Young) Teacher
[Sunmi’s crying]
I have a favor to ask you.
[Gyeongju groans in pain]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[Gyeongju groans in pain]
(Youngchan) Why, where does it hurt?
(Gyeongju) No, it’s okay
That...
Did you have a good time?
Oh, my mom?
Oh, they say they'll come back tomorrow
(Youngchan) Baby clothes and lobster towels
They said they would need it
Oh, tell them thank you
(Youngchan) Yes
Honey, where does it hurt?
Does it hurt a lot? Should I call the doctor?
(Gyeongju) Ah...
Oh no
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
(Sabi) Hello
(Youngchan) Hello
This
[Calm music]
[Gyeongju’s comfortable breathing]
I think I'll buy it, teacher.
There's more
I really think I will buy it, thank you
My father threw it in the trash can.
(Sabi) I was going to follow you and give it back to you.
Looking at the contents
Given the context, it seems like it's from a mother.
(Gyeongju Department) ‘Discharged from hospital’
'I asked the mothers'
‘They said we need something like this’
[Nostalgic music]
‘If you need anything more’
'Contact me'
[Gyeongju’s Cry]
(Youngchan) Ah
here
Are you okay?
[Gyeongju’s Cry]
Did it hurt a lot?
It's okay, it's okay
[Gyeongju’s Cry]
[Sunmi’s crying]
(Sanghyeon) It’s 7:20
(Lee Young) Please give me 10 more minutes.
thank you
(Sanghyun) Oh, we’re okay.
Teacher Oh I-young, are you okay?
Even if I prepare from now on, it will take 30 more minutes.
(Bori) Professor Jo Jun-mo
You're not the type of person who understands this.
I'm sure you'll scream a lot again.
(Lee Young) I will tell the professor.
[Call connection tone]
Professor, surgery on patient Geum Seon-mi.
(Junmo) Uh, I’ll arrive in exactly 5 minutes.
The surgery will start right away.
(Lee Young) Oh, that’s right, I don’t think that will work.
Why, what's the problem?
(Lee Young) It’s me.
Uh...
I skipped one wrap in the morning.
(Sanghyeon) Abgar, Abgar, Abgar
(Lee Young) ABGA
(Junmo) You left out Abgar?
(Lee Young) Yes
That's right now in the anesthesiology department.
ABGA is in progress as an emergency.
A little time...
(Junmo) Hey!
what the hell are you
Are you going to get your mind back to work, huh?
I have a conference meeting today!
I told you there was no delay
How many times, how many times do you say it?
Oh, please don't be late this time.
I made a request like that.
Wow! Seriously, what on earth are you doing?
What on earth is this guy doing!
(Lee Young) I’m really sorry
I will never let something like this happen again.
(Junmo) Hey, you idiot!
(Lee Young) Yes, that’s right, I’m stupid.
sorry
[Call end sound]
[Lee Young sighs]
[Medical device operation sound]
thank you
[Calm music]
[Sunmi’s whimpering sound]
(Sanghyun) Let’s start anesthesia.
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
[Sunmi sighs nervously]
[Medical device operation sound]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
(Junmo) Oh Iyoung, aren’t you concentrating?
I'm late because of you, huh?
Why do you keep looking at your watch?
(Lee Young) I’m sorry
(Junmo) It’s a little late today
(Lee Young) It’s time to come
(Announcement) This is the Department of Pathology.
This is the surgery for patient Geum Seon-mi in room 10, right?
(Junmo) Yes, that’s right
(Announcement) The organization that sent you
Are you ovarian?
(Junmo) Yes
(Announcement) First of all,
In the section...
[Sunmi’s mock sobbing sound]
(Junmo) I’ll tell you well about the results.
Take care of your facial expressions so you don't get surprised...
[Sound of automatic door opening]
[Sound of running footsteps]
[Junmo’s sigh]
If only I had prepared for surgery at that speed.
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST-Continued]
[Lee Young’s heavy breathing]
(Sunmi) Thank you teacher
Thank you teacher, thank you so much
[Sunmi mocks crying]
[Sunmi’s crying sound]
[Seonmibu’s sobbing sound]
(Sunmi) Stop crying
[Sunmi mocks crying]
Thank you for your hard work
[Sunmi’s wife sighs in relief]
[Sunmi mocks crying]
(Junmo) Because the ovarian lump is not in a good shape
I was worried
Both are B9 people
(Eunmi) I think the bleeding is okay too.
I'll finish it well, Professor.
(Junmo) Okay
Please count the gauze
(Dahye) It’s my first surgery tomorrow morning.
What should I do if I don’t get permission?
This is the most basic of basics.
(Nanjing) I’m sorry
I'll take it right now
(Dahye) Yes
[Call end tone]
[Mouse operation sound]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[eerie sound effect]
[creaking sound]
[Mouse operation sound]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Ok-Im’s labored breathing]
[Calm music]
[Nanjing’s sigh]
[Sound of a ballpoint pen snapping]
[Sound of toilet flushing]
(Nanjing) Grandmother
(Okim) Oh my, you’re surprised.
[Calm music]
It's 9 o'clock
Oh my, our flower line is very classy.
- Are you ready?
- (Okim) Ying
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Okim) It’s okay
Why is it still over 300?
(Ok Im) It’s okay if I can’t be discharged.
I knew so
Why?
Where did you feel uncomfortable?
It was uncomfortable
My heart, Seonsangnimhanty
(Ok Im) I went out yesterday during the day
12 Saying that it has turned around
But I couldn't make it past 8 turns at night.
8 laps?
Oh, grandma, I just
Just...
You shouldn't say things like that.
[Calm music]
(Okim) Oh my, the rice isn’t even cooked properly.
It's not cool to just walk around with the smell all blowing on you.
Even though I am not a doctor
I just said I couldn't be discharged from the hospital.
How many times did our captain ask?
Oh my, I didn't do that.
It's my fault, don't worry about it
(Nanjing) What about the wedding?
So what about the wedding?
(Okim) Even if I don’t write
last night
I called to say I couldn’t go.
I canceled it
(Nanjing) You canceled the wedding?
(Okim) I wish I had Gracorom right away.
You wouldn't have bothered our flower ship.
go out too
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
[sigh]
Like our flower ship
When flowers bloom on your face
If I can't be kind, I'll end up doing it in the middle of the day.
If you miss it, if you wait, it's okay.
Bye
When the flowers of life fade
Whatever the Son of Man is, he is the last.
There is no next time
I don't have time
[Calm music - continued]
[Nankyung’s sobbing sound]
Look at it positively when you can
Tongue when you can
I'll miss you when I die
Miscellaneous things to see
Our flower ship is proud
Be sure to buy it
Don’t regret it.
yes
(Ok Im) Don’t worry about me
From now on, I walk hard every day.
I’ll stay with a lot of food too.
Ah, grandma
That walking thing
Walk just enough to not strain your knees.
Uh, twice a day for 30 minutes.
Just walk that far.
Eat as balanced a meal as possible
Chew thoroughly before eating
You should never overeat
I'm sorry
(Okim) Oh my?
They say all kinds of things on the flower ship.
[Okim’s laughter]
[Knocking sound]
(Ok-Im’s husband) Oh my, Mr. Ok-Im.
Why are you alone?
Oh, what kind of person is secretly getting surgery?
Oh, is our Ok-Im okay?
Yes, the surgery went well.
are you okay now
Ah, mom!
[Ok-Im’s granddaughter sighs]
No matter what, to us
What if I don't talk?
It's a wedding and it's noisy again
(Ok-Im’s granddaughter) Grandmother
Do you know how surprised we are?
Oh, your granddaughter?
Ah, yes, yes
What should I do, the wedding is canceled?
It's okay
When you get discharged, you can catch me again.
[Nankyung’s light smile]
You even canceled your wedding because of your grandmother.
(Ok-Im’s granddaughter) Ah...
Of course
What should I do when the bride can't come?
Yes?
(Okim’s daughter) [Laughing] Huh? Ah, there
No, that's not the priest.
It's me
[Tingling sound effect]
[Okim’s daughter laughs]
[bright music]
(Okim) Naga bride
[Okim’s laughter]
What in the world?
What's a wedding without a bride?
You have to go out to have a wedding.
(Ok-Im’s husband) With the restaurant
All photos have been cancelled.
Oh, you can’t cancel this rice cake.
That's good, huh?
Young-ah, to the people at this hospital.
Please give me this rice cake.
(Ok Im) Oh my gosh
Everyone just can't get enough blood.
I jump at you day and night
Our flower Seon-sang
Give me two... three!
(Ok-Im’s granddaughter) Three?
[Ok-Im’s husband’s laughter]
Here
thank you
thank you grandma
[sniffling sound]
(Jaeil) Hey, hey, hey, quickly, quickly, quickly
It's now, they say it's changing now
(Nanjing) What? Change what?
[Nankyung’s surprised groan]
[humorous music]
(Sabi) Oh my
It's not Eom Jae-il
(Nanjing) Somehow it didn’t work at all.
What are warm words
(Lee Young) Did anyone believe that?
(Sabi) Nurse Oh Ji-young
The footsteps that always come running first
faster than anyone else
The hand that touches the painful area
It was a greater comfort than any other words.
Not only Nurse Oh Ji-young
To other medical staff
Thank you
(Lee Young) Yes, there are other Eom Jae-il people.
(Japan) I wanted to take a proof photo and post it on Instagram.
I also washed my hair
(Nanjing) Good.
(Sabi) What?
(Nanjing) Today is the day to take OBGY photos.
Group photo this year
(Lee Young) Wow...
Wow, I hate it so much
[Lee Young sighs]
[upbeat music]
[Sound of bustling]
(together) hello
(Jeongmin) Is everyone here?
(Steamboat) It will come
(Photographer) And at the very end there
teacher standing
(Residence in Japan) Oh I-young
you, you
yes, yes
Would you like to move forward just one space?
[Lee Young sighs]
(Photographer) Thank you
(Sabi) But the group photo
Why not film in March and film in May?
The guy who gives up, the guy who resigns
Giving time to the guy who's running away
(Sabi) Ah
When stuffed into a photo
Both those who left and those who stayed are embarrassed, right?
You can't pierce it with a punch.
But why don’t you come with your wife?
(Eunmi) Oh, there is a conference with the surgeon.
They say it's not over yet
I think he'll be here in 5 minutes
(Kiseon) Then, driver.
Please take a picture between us first.
Let’s just take a picture of the mountains and each other, okay?
Oh, really?
(Jeongmin) Driver
Please take a picture between us first.
(Photographer) Yes, I understand.
Okay then
(Jeongmin) Oh, are all the residents here?
Gu Do-won, where is Gu Do-won?
Can't you see the chief?
(Dowon) Oh, I’m here!
We're all here
sorry
- (Photographer) Is everyone here?
- (Dowon) Yes
(Photographer) Yes, I will take a picture then.
Now, when you say one, two, three, make kimchi.
Hey, not kimchi.
(Jae-Jae) How about using mites?
I suggest you
[Doctors laugh]
- (Kiseon) What kind of mite is this?
- (Eunmi) The mite is okay.
Is it good?
Come on, let's do it.
Yes, please do it, I will definitely see it.
(Lee Young) I don’t think I can do it
Because I want to do something else
(Photographer) Okay, then, one, two, three.
mites are coming
One, two, three!
(together) Mite!
[camera shutter sound]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
‘Life as a Major’ OST-Continued]
(Jae-il) Knock, I heard a rumor.
You have the same tastes as me
(Jooyoung) Is there anyone you can meet at the hospital?
(Do-won) Oh I-young
(Jooyoung) Who likes it, what is it?
Haven't you heard of this?
(Jaeil) I like it a lot too
(Namkyung) Hey, are you that good?
It’s exciting, we’re eating together.
(Lee Young) There is one person
(Jooyoung) Oh, who is it?
How about trying this one, Oh I-young?
(Sabi) It’s completely unfair.
There is someone who wants to do it
What is a person who wants to quit doing?
Are you giving me a useless chance?
(Lee Young) I can’t do this anymore
(Namkyung) Oh I-young, that’s what made my heart float, it floated
This time, Seo Jeong-min
I don't think I'll just get over it
(Sabi) Then, Professor Seo Jeong-min’s surgery was
Who's going in? Am I going?
(Jaeil) We’re friends, so please understand.
(Lee Young) I’m going to quit soon, but what about my friend?
(Lee Young) I’m sorry
(Jeongmin) If you can’t do it,
It's not up to us
It's for new mothers.
If it's for the baby, do it.
(Junwan) When I was born
I hope it's around 2kg.
Please save me, sir.
(Bohyun) Please
Please let me meet my baby
(Dowon) I use it when I’m scared and scared like now.
There is one cheat key